incomesensor.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy-IncomeSensor

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which IncomeSensor.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.incomesensor.com/ website (“Site”,”Blog”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by IncomeSensor.com.

Personal identification information

I may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit my site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources I make available on my Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address. Users may, however, visit my Site anonymously. I will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to me. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

I may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with my Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to my Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

My Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

IncomeSensor.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics I think will be of interest to them.  
– To send periodic emails  
I may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to my mailing list, they will receive emails that may include Blog news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, I include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact me via my Site.

How we protect your information

I adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information.

Sharing your personal information

I do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. I may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with my business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.I may use third party service providers to help me operate my business and the Site or administer activities on my behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on my Site that link to the sites and services of my partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. I do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from my Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to my Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on my Site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners including Google, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Changes to this privacy policy

IncomeSensor.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Contacting Me

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
IncomeSensor.com

http://www.incomesensor.com/

Fathi@incomesensor.com

This document was last updated on  February 09, 2014
